A Guide to the Papers of Homer Stille Cummings, ca.1850-1955
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
- SERIES IV: SPEECHES, 1886-1950 & ARTICLES, 1918-1945
  - Article - monograph - "We Can Prevent Crime" (4 articles reprinted from Liberty) (by Homer Stille Cummings) (Box 233)
  - Report: "Statement and Recommendations of the Attorney General, 1937" (by Homer Stille Cummings) 1937 (Box 233)
  - Printed Address: "Attorney General Cummings' Address at the Washington Institute," in the American Bar Association Journal(by Homer Stille Cummings) (Box 233)
  - Article - monograph: "Extending the Rule-Making Power to Federal Criminal Procedure" (by Homer Stille Cummings; includes correspondence) 1938 December (Box 233)
  - Article: "The Value of Judicial Conferences in the Federal Circuits" (by Homer Stille Cummings; by correspondence) 1938 December (Box 233)
  - Article - monograph: "Nature of the Amending Process" (by Homer Stille Cummings) 1938 (Box 233)
  - Report: Statement and Recommendations of the Attorney General, 1938" (by Homer Stille Cummings) 1938 (Box 233)
  - Article: "Bar Presents Resolutions in memory of Justice Cardoza to the Supreme Court, remarks of Attorney General Cummings in presenting resolutions" in American Bar Association Journal(by Homer Stille Cummings) 1938 (Box 233)
  - Article: "Why Alcatraz is a Success" in Collier's(by Homer Stille Cummings) 1939 July 29 (Box 233)
  - Article: "The New Criminal Rules - Another Triumph of the Democratic Process" (by Homer Stille Cummings; drafts & correspondence) 1945 February-December (Box 233)
  - Article by Homer Stille Cummings: A review of After-Conduct of Discharged Offenders by Sheldon Glueck and Eleanor T. Glueck in Harvard University 1945 September (Box 233)
  - Article by Homer Stille Cummings: "The New Criminal Rules - Another Triumph of the Democratic Process" in American Bar Association Journal1945 May (Box 233)
- SERIES V: LITERARY PAPERS, Note: The diaries marked with an asterisk have been microfilmed
  - Personal and Political Diary of Homer Stille Cummings *1919 April 7-1928 November 5 (Box 234)
  - Personal and Political Diary of Homer Stille Cummings *1932 January 3-1933 April 7 (Box 234)
  - Extracts of letters: See diary for 1944 1932-1938 (Box 234)
  - Personal and Political Diary of Homer Stille Cummings *1933 April 10-December 31 (Box 234)
  - Personal and Political Diary of Homer Stille Cummings 1934 (Box 234)
  - Travel Diary & Play, Hawaii *1934 July 22-September 5 (Box 234)
  - Personal and Political Diary of Homer Stille Cummings *1935 (Box 234)
  - Personal and Political Diary of Homer Stille Cummings *1936 (Box 235)
  - Personal and Political Diary of Homer Stille Cummings *1937 (Box 235)
  - Personal and Political Diary of Homer Stille Cummings *1938 (Box 235)
  - Personal and Political Diary of Homer Stille Cummings *1939 (Box 235)
  - Personal and Political Diary of Homer Stille Cummings *1940 (Box 235)
  - Personal and Political Diary of Homer Stille Cummings *1941 (Box 235)
  - Personal and Political Diary of Homer Stille Cummings *1942 (Box 236)
  - [Housekeeping Diary?] ca. 1942-1945 (Box 236)
  - Personal and Political Diary of Homer Stille Cummings *1943 (Box 236)
  - Personal and Political Diary of Homer Stille Cummings, extracts of letters *1944, 1932-1938 (Box 236)
  - Personal and Political Diary of Homer Stille Cummings *1945 (Box 236)
  - Personal and Political Diary of Homer Stille Cummings *1946 (Box 237)
  - Personal and Political Diary of Homer Stille Cummings *1947 (Box 237)
  - Personal and Political Diary of Homer Stille Cummings *1948 (Box 237)
  - Personal and Political Diary of Homer Stille Cummings *1949 (Box 237)
  - Personal and Political Diary of Homer Stille Cummings *1950 (Box 237)
  - Personal and Political Diary of Homer Stille Cummings *1951 (Box 238)
  - Personal and Political Diary of Homer Stille Cummings *1952 (Box 238)
  - Personal and Political Diary of Homer Stille Cummings *1953 (Box 238)
  - Personal and Political Diary of Homer Stille Cummings *1954 (Box 238)
  - Personal and Political Diary of Homer Stille Cummings *1955 (Box 238)
  - Personal and Political Diary of Homer Stille Cummings *1956 January 25-August 20 (Box 238)
  - Appointments Book 1926 (Box 239)
  - Appointments Book 1931-1939 (Box 239)
  - Appointments Book 1945, 1946-1949 (Box 239)
  - Appointments Book 1950-1955 (Box 239)
  - [Medical Diary?] 1943-1944 (Box 239)
  - Book Reviews of Homer Stille Cummings' book, Liberty Under Law and Administration 1934-1935 (Box 240)
  - Federal Justice, by Homer Stille Cummings and Carl McFarland, title page and introduction and Chapters I-XIV [ca. 1936], TMs (draft); 5 folders (Box 240)
  - Federal Justice, by Homer Stille Cummings and Carl McFarland, Chapters XV-XXIV [1936], TMs (draft); 5 folders (Box 241)
  - Federal Justice, by Homer Stille Cummings and Carl McFarland, Chapters I-XX [1936], TMs (tentative final draft); 4 folders (Box 242)
  - Federal Justice, by Homer Stille Cummings and Carl McFarland, Chapters XVIII-XXIV [ca. 1936], TMs (tentative final draft); 2 folders (Box 243)
  - Federal Justice, by Homer Stille Cummings and Carl McFarland, Chapters I-XVI [ca. 1936], TMs (carbon; final draft, no. 4); 2 folders (Box 243)
  - Federal Justice, by Homer Stille Cummings and Carl McFarland, Chapters XVIII-XXIV [ca. 1936], TMs (carbon; final draft, no. 4) (Box 244)
  - Federal Justice, by Homer Stille Cummings and Carl McFarland, Chapters I-XXIV [1936], TMs (carbon; final draft, no. 5); 3 folders (Box 244)
  - Outlines of Preface, and Memoranda re: Federal Justice, by Homer Stille Cummings and Carl McFarland 1936, TMs (carbon) (Box 245)
  - Lists of Persons to whom copies of Federal Justice, by Homer Stille Cummings and Carl McFarland were sent; letters of thanks for the copies 1936 December-1941 February (Box 245)
  - Correspondence re: Publication, Distribution, Sales and REviews of Federal Justice, by Homer Stille Cummings and Carl McFarland 1935 September-1936 December, 4 folders (Box 245)
  - Correspondence re: Publication, Distribution, Sales, and Reviews of Federal Justice, by Homer Stille Cummings and Carl McFarland 1936 December-1938, 4 folders (Box 246)
  - Correspondence and reviews of Federal Justice, by Homer Stille Cummings and Carl McFarland 1937 January-August, 2 folders (Box 246)
  - Correspondence and reviews of Federal Justice, by Homer Stille Cummings and Carl McFarland 1937 September-1939 January (Box 247)
  - Correspondence re: Federal Justice, by Homer Stille Cummings and Carl McFarland, including letters of thanks for copies of the book 1936 December-1937 April (Box 247)
  - Correspondence re: Reviews of Federal Justice, by Homer Stille Cummings and Carl McFarland 1936-1937 (Box 247)
  - Reviews of Federal Justice, by Homer Stille Cummings and Carl McFarland 1937 (Box 247)
  - Notes, table of contents, title page, and suggestions re: The Biography of a Department, the Department of Justice of the United States, 1933-1938, by [Carl McFarland] 1938 [ca. September] (Box 248)
  - Draft with holograph corrections, [ The Biography of a Department, the Department of Justice of the United States], "Report of the Activities of the Department of Justice," by [Carl McFarland] 1938 [ca. September], TMs (draft); 3 folders (Box 248)
  - List of files for The Biography of a Department by Carl McFarland 1938 [ca. September] (Box 248)
  - Correspondence re: Selected Papers of Homer Cummings edited by Carl B. Swisher 1938 September-1941 October (Box 248)
  - Attorney General Personal File - The Tired Sea(acknowledgements H-Z) 1939 December-1940 February (Box 249)
  - Attorney general Personal File - Miscellaneous Memos and Correspondence re: The Tired Sea 1940-1943 (Box 249)
  - Research file of Carl McFarland re: proposed study of military law ca. 1804-ca. 1935, 2 folders (Box 249)
  - Research file of Carl McFarland re: proposed study of military law ca. 1861-ca. 1936 (Box 250)
  - Memoranda of [Carl McFarland] re: President's power to supress and prevent internal disturbances ca. 1935, 2 folders (Box 250)
  - Memoranda of Carl McFarland re: Power of the President to use Army, Navy, and National Guard in Internal Affairs ca. 1935 (Box 250)
  - Analysis of Annual Report of the Attorney General, 1870-1935 [ca. 1935] (Box 251)
  - "Statuatory development of the Office of the Attorney General and the Department of Justice" [by Carl McFarland] [ca. 1936?], TMs (Box 251)
  - Notes on readings re: Military law [ca. 1939?], AN (Box 251)
  - Alphabetical card index of cases digested by Vernon L. Wilkinson for Carl McFarland's study on military law ca. 1939 (Box 251)
  - Completed Chapters I-III of a proposed Litigation History of the Lands Division, Department of Justice and Correspondence 1952 (Box 252)
  - First Draft for a proposed Litigation History of the Lands Division, Department of Justice re: Land patents ca. 1953 (Box 252)
  - Resource Material: Memoranda, Excerpts, and Precedents for a proposed Litigation History of the Lands Division, Department of Justice, mainly re: Appellate Section 1828-1958 (Box 252)
  - Resource Material: Memoranda, Excerpts, and Precedents for a proposed Litigation History of the Lands Division, Department of Justice, mainly re: Indian affairs 1855-1953; 1909-1952; 1949-1953, 3 folders (Box 252)
  - Resource Material: Memoranda, Excerpts, and Precedents for a proposed Litigation History of the Lands Division, Department of Justice, mainly re: Indian affairs 1950-1954, 2 folders (Box 253)
  - Resource Material: Memoranda, Excerpts, and Precedents for a proposed Litigation History of the Lands Division, Department of Justice, mainly re: Indian affairs 1950-1954 (Box 253)
  - Resource Material: Memoranda, Excerpts, and Precedents for a proposed Litigation History of the Lands Division, Department of Justice, mainly re: transportation grants of land 1952 (Box 253)
  - Resource Material: Memoranda, Excerpts, and Precedents for a proposed Litigation History of the Lands Division, Department of Justice, mainly re: Land acquisition 1909-1952 (Box 253)
  - Resource Material: Memoranda, Excerpts, and Precedents for a proposed Litigation History of the Lands Division, Department of Justice, mainly re: Land acquisition 1917-1953 (Box 254)
  - Resource Material: Memoranda, Excerpts, and Precedents for a proposed Litigation History of the Lands Division, Department of Justice, mainly re: Legislation and General Selection, Land acquisition 1938-1953 (Box 254)
  - Resource Material: Memoranda, Excerpts, and Precedents for a proposed Litigation History of the Lands Division, Department of Justice, mainly re: Land acquisition ca. 1953 (Box 254)
  - Resource Material: Memoranda, Excerpts, and Precedents for a proposed Litigation History of the Lands Division, Department of Justice, mainly re: land acquisition 1953 (Box 255)
  - Resource Material: Memoranda, Excerpts, and Precedents for a proposed Litigation History of the Lands Division, Department of Justice, mainly re: Organization and personnel 1937-1953 (Box 255)
  - Resource Material: Memoranda, Excerpts, and Precedents for a proposed Litigation History of the Lands Division, Department of Justice, mainly re: Organization and personnel, territorial and Indian affairs 1947-1953 (Box 255)
  - Resource Material: Memoranda, Excerpts, and Precedents for a proposed Litigation History of the Lands Division, Department of Justice, mainly re: Territorial lands and Indian affairs 1953 (Box 255)
- SERIES VI: LAW FIRM PAPERS
  - Cummings and Lockwood: Partnership Agreements 1934-1940 (Box 256)
  - Cummings and Lockwood: Retirement Payments for Homer Stille Cummings 1932 July-1934 September (Box 256)
  - Cummings and Lockwood: Miscellaneous Correspondence 1935 June-1955 March (Box 256)
  - Cummings and Lockwood: Miscellaneous Papers n.d. (Box 256)
  - Account Book of Cummings and Lockwood; and Cummings and Stanley 1909-1933; 1939-1944 (Box 256)
  - Responses to announcement of formation of hte firm of Cummings and Stanley 1939 January 28-June 14 (Box 257)
  - Correspondenc of Homer Stille Cummings with William Stanley 1940 June-1946 May (Box 257)
  - Correspondenc of Homer Stille Cummings with Mrs. William Stanley 1946 June-1955 November (Box 257)
  - Correspondenc & Papers of Homer Stille Cummings re: William Stanley's financial holdings, debts, taxes, etc. 1946 May-October (Box 257)
  - Correspondenc of Homer Stille Cummings re: Death of William Stanley 1946 July-1947 January (Box 257)
  - Cummings, Stanley, Truitt and Cross: Financial records 1943-1945 (Box 257)
  - Cummings, Stanley, Truitt and Cross: Financial records, includes fees, expenses, profit sharing 1947 May-1948 December (Box 257)
  - Cummings, Stanley, Truitt and Cross: Financial records includes individual members' earnings 1949 (Box 257)
  - Cummings, Stanley, Truitt and Cross: Financial records includes individual members' earnings 1950-1955, 4 folders (Box 258)
  - Cummings, Stanley, Truitt and Cross: Miscellaneous Memoranda of Homer Stille Cummings 1946, n.d. (Box 258)
  - Cummings, Stanley, Truitt and Cross: Calculations, Memos, Contracts, and Partnership Agreements 1947-1950 (Box 258)
  - Cummings, Stanley, Truitt and Cross: Replies to announcement of address change 1947 May-July (Box 258)
  - Cummings, Stanley, Truitt and Cross: Correspondence, Memos and Papers re: separation of Mac Asbill from the firm 1949 March-1950 January (Box 258)
  - Correspondence and papers re: Julian Freret 1951 (Box 258)
  - Cummings, Stanley, Truitt and Cross: Miscellaneous correspondence, memos, and charts relating to breakdown of profit sharing and general firm revenues 1953 (Box 258)
  - Cummings, Stanley, Truitt and Cross: Address lists n.d. (Box 258)
  - Cummings and Stanley Ship Purchase Program n.d. (Box 258)
  - Ledger 1943-1947 (Box 258)
- SERIES VII: MISCELLANEOUS PAPERS
  - List of autographs of Homer Stille Cummings, Attorney General of the United States 1933 March 4-1939 January 2 (Box 259)
  - Correspondence and papers re: Biographical information re: Homer Stille Cummings 1933 August-1942 July, 2 folders (Box 259)
  - "Biographical Sketches of hte Attorneys General - Edmund Randolph to Tom C. Clark," prepared by Arthur Robb 1946 May 15 (Box 259)
  - Correspondence and Papers re: Yale Law School Directory Questionnaire, which contains biographical information re: Homer Stille Cummings 1947 January-March (Box 259)
  - Photostatic copy of questionnaire of Yale Law School with answers contains biographical information re: Homer Stille Cummings 1947 March 5 (Box 259)
  - Correspondence and Papers re: biographical information of Homer Stille Cummings 1949-1951 (Box 259)
  - Correspondence and Papers re: Frank Schroth's speech in honor of Homer Stille Cummings on his eighteenth birthday, includes biographical information 1950 August (Box 259)
  - Correspondence and Papers, including biographical information re: Homer Stille Cummings 1953 January-October (Box 259)
  - Certificates 1911-1956 (Box 260)
  - Dollar bills and German bank notes n.d. (Box 260)
  - Legal Document: Henry Ward empowering Jeremiah Whipple as Justice of the Peace 1775 June 19 (Box 260)
  - Legal documents singed by Edmund Randolph and Hardin Perkins 1787 December 10 (Box 260)
  - Programs 1910 September-1925 February (Box 260)
  - Programs 1933 March-1950 April & n.d., 4 folders (Box 261)
  - Picturesque Stamford 1641-1892 (Box 262)
  - Complimentary Dinner to the Honorable Homer Stille Cummings 1925 (Box 262)
  - Official Inaugural Program 1937, 2 copies (Box 262)
  - Souvenirs and Mementoes ca. 1922-1949 (Box 263)
  - Stamps, First Issue, with correspondence 1934-1938, 4 folders (Box 263)
- SERIES VIII: PHOTOGRAPHS, 1870-1953
  - Photographs - A 1930-1953 (Box 264)
  - Photographs - B 1924-1948 (Box 264)
  - Photographs - C 1887-1937 (Box 264)
  - Photographs - D 1913-1952 (Box 264)
  - Photographs - James Dinkins 1861-1928 (Box 264)
  - Photographs - E 1935-1939 (Box 265)
  - Photographs - F [1900]-1945 (Box 265)
  - Photographs - G 1916-1951 (Box 265)
  - Photographs - H 1923-1950 (Box 265)
  - Photographs - I [1920]-1934 (Box 265)
  - Photographs - Harold Israel 1924-1948 (Box 265)
  - Photographs - J 1934-1946 (Box 265)
  - Photographs - K 1934-1946 (Box 266)
  - Photographs - L 1917-1945 (Box 266)
  - Photographs - Charles Lockwood [1905]-1946 (Box 266)
  - Photographs - M-McLean 1913-1945 (Box 266)
  - Photographs - McMahon-N 1920-1950 (Box 266)
  - Photographs - O, P, Q 1920-1938 (Box 267)
  - Photographs - R 1928-1937 (Box 267)
  - Photograph - Eleanor Roosevelt 1934 (Box 267)
  - Photographs - Franklin D. Roosevelt 1917-1936 (Box 267)
  - Photographs - S 1934-1945 (Box 267)
  - Photographs - Alfred Smith 1930 (Box 267)
  - Photographs - Adlai Stevenson 1953 (Box 267)
  - Photographs - T 1916-1945 (Box 268)
  - Photographs - Harry S. Truman 1944-1948 (Box 268)
  - Photographs - V 1934-1944 (Box 268)
  - Photographs - W 1916-1942 (Box 268)
  - Photographs - Woodrow Wilson 1918-1920 (Box 268)
  - Photographs - Identity undetermined 1934-1937 (Box 268)
  - Photographs - Professional portraits 1903-1942; 1936-1937, 3 folders (Box 269)
  - Photographs - Homer Stille Cummings with colleagues 1919-1930, 2 folders (Box 270)
  - Photographs - Dedication of the new Justice Building 1934 October 25 (Box 270)
  - Photographs - Homer Stille Cummings with colleagues 1934-1939, 6 folders (Box 270)
  - Photographs - Miscellaneous group portraits, including U.s. Supreme Court 1904-1936 (Box 271)
  - Photographs - Patents and ancestors [1870]-1902 (Box 271)
  - Photographs - Old Family Residences 1870-1896 (Box 271)
  - Photographs - Uriah Cummings' inventions n.d. (Box 271)
  - Photographs - Uriah Cummings' cement factory n.d. (Box 271)
  - Photographs from family photo album, including shots of Homer Stille Cummings' parents, groups of children, buildings and landscapes [1800-1890] (Box 271)
  - Photographs - Homer Stille Cummings' childhood and youth 1870-1906 (Box 272)
  - Photographs - Group photographs, early acquaintances of Homer Stille Cummings 1880-1904 (Box 272)
  - Photographs - Yale students and professors, including reunions 1891-1946 (Box 272)
  - Photographs - Ruthven, family rsort, in Akron, NY 1898; 1903-1932, 2 folders (Box 272)
  - Photographs - Villa Octavia, Greenwich, CT 1929-1930 (Box 273)
  - Photographs - Washington, D.C. home of Homer Stille Cummings [1933] (Box 273)
  - Photographs - Rock Ridge Ave, Greenwich, CT, home of Homer Stille Cummings [1935?] (Box 273)
  - Photographs - Dickinson Cummings [1900-1920] (Box 274)
  - Photographs - Cecilia Cummings n.d. (Box 274)
  - Photographs - Family miscellaneous 1943-1952 (Box 274)
  - Photographs - Julia Cummings n.d. (Box 274)
  - Photographs - Helen Smith Cummings n.d. (Box 274)
  - Photographs - European trip of Homer Stille Cummings and wife Cecilia 1926 (Box 274)
  - Photographs - Lake George, Lake Champlain and Saratoga trip 1928 September (Box 274)
  - Photographs - Homer Stille Cummings and Cecilia in New England 1928 September (Box 274)
  - Photographs - Trip to Southwest and San Diego 1929 (Box 274)
  - Photographs - Camping 1929 (Box 275)
  - Photographs & Postcards from trip to West Indies 1930 (Box 275)
  - Photographs & postcards - Spain & France 1931 (Box 275)
  - Photographs & postcards - Europe 1931 (Box 265)
  - Photographs & postcards - Mid-East trip 1931 (Box 275)
  - Photographs & postcards - Trip to Europe and Mid-East 1931 (Box 275)
  - Photographs - England 1931 (Box 275)
  - Photographs - Vacation trip to Montana, Hollywood, Hawaii, includes shots of Cummigns with James Cagney, Jack Warner, Joe E. Brown 1934 (Box 275)
  - Photographs - Homer & Cecilia Cummings 1936-1937 (Box 275)
  - Photographs of vacation to Minacqua, Wisconsin 1938 August (Box 275)
  - Photographs - Homer & Julia Cummings, vacations [1935-1945] (Box 275)
  - Photographs - Homer & Julia Cummings, vacation [1935-1945] (Box 276)
  - Photographs - Golf at Pinehurst, North Carolina 1934-1935; [ca. 1935-1940]; 1937 (Box 276)
  - Photographs - Golf at Pinehurst, North Carolina 1938-1941, 2 folders (Box 277)
  - Photographs - Golf at Pinehurst, North Carolina, Emerson Humphrey, photographer n.d. (Box 277)
  - Photographs - Homer & Julia Cummings, their home, some vacation shots [1942-1951] (Box 277)
  - Postcards of architectural monuments n.d. (Box 277)
  - Postcards of paintings, art work n.d. (Box 277)
  - Postcards & photographs of South America n.d. (Box 277)
  - Photographs - Scenes from Great Britain, primarily Edinburgh, Scotland n.d. (Box 277)
  - Photographs - Pinehurst, North Carolina n.d. (Box 277)
  - Photographs - Cummings' automobile (?) 1939 (Box 277)
  - Miscellaneous photographs and pictures, United States n.d. (Box 278)
  - Photographs - U.S.-general, family, miscellaneous unidentified n.d. (Box 278)
  - Negatives of photographs n.d. (Box 278)
  - Artistic drawings & reproductions n.d. (Box 278)
  - Miscellaneous drawings & poetry n.d. (Box 278)
  - Photo album - Photos of Homer Stille Cummings' parents, cousins and early acquaintances 1872-1901 (Box 279)
  - Photo album - Photos of Homer Stille Cummings' youth, including pictures of father's factory, family photos, early residence [1880-1890] (Box 279)
  - Photo album - Photos of vacation trip to Minocqua, Wisconsin 1938, 2 items (Box 279)
  - Photo album - Photos from trip to Hawaii, Rocky Mountains 1934 (Box 280)
  - Photo album - Photographs of Federal prisons 1938 December (Box 280)
  - Photo album - Drawings of Federal prisons 1938 December (Box 280)
  - Portrait of Uriah Cummings 1899 (Box-folder 69:1)
  - Members of the Democratic National Committee, taken in front of the White House 1915 December 8 (Box-folder 69:1)
  - Jackson Day Banquet 1920 January 8 (Box-folder 69:1)
  - national Democratic Club Testimonial Dinner to Homer Stille Cummings, Commodore Hotel, New York (Box-folder 69:1)
  - Portrait of John Garner 1920 April 30 (Box-folder 69:1)
  - Portrait of G.W. Wheeler, retired Chief Justice of the Court of Errors 1932 July 28 (Box-folder 69:1)
  - Testimonial Dinner to Homer Stille Cummings as Attorney General at the STratfield Hotel, Bridgeport, Connecticut 1933 April 15 (Box-folder 69:1)
  - Signed group portrait of Franklin Delano Roosevelt's cabinet 1933, 2 items (Box-folder 69:1)
  - Homer Stille Cummings at military reception, Chicago New World's Fair [1933] June 8 (Box-folder 69:1)
  - Signed group portrait of the U.S. Supreme Court 1934 February, 2 items (Box-folder 69:1)
  - Signed group portrait of the U.S. Supreme Court 1934 February, 2 items (Box-folder 69:1)
  - Franklin Delano Roosevelt signing crime bills, Homer Stille Cummings and Hoover watching 1934 May 19 (Box-folder 69:1)
  - Signed portrait drawing of Franklin Delano Roosevelt 1934 October 22, 3 items (Box-folder 69:1)
  - Dedication of New Department of Justice Building 1934 October 25, 2 items (Box-folder 69:1)
  - Signed portrait of Aron Fitzgerald 1934 November 22 (Box-folder 69:2)
  - Portrait of Homer Stille Cummings in Hawaii [1934] (Box-folder 69:2)
  - Portrait of Homer Stille Cummings in Hawaii [1934] (Box-folder 69:2)
  - Composit photograph of members of Franklin Delano Roosevelt's cabinet 1934 (Box-folder 69:2)
  - Honorary Dinner for Franklin Delano Roosevelt given by Vice-President John Garner, Hotel Washington, Washington, D.C. 1935 January 16 (Box-folder 69:2)
  - Signed group portraits of Homer Stille Cummings and his associates at the Department of Justice 1935 March 20, 4 items (Box-folder 69:2)
  - Signed portrait of A.T. Muller 1935 July 15 (Box-folder 69:2)
  - Signed portrait of Kimbrough Stone 1935 September 20 (Box-folder 69:2)
  - Homer Stille Cummings at the opening of the Government Baseball League 1936 April 25 (Box-folder 69:2)
  - Homer Stille Cummings delivering address at Illinois State Fair 1936 August 20 (Box-folder 69:2)